<root>
	<styles>
		<include src="s2r://panorama/styles/dotastyles.vcss_c" />
		<include src="s2r://panorama/styles/play.vcss_c" />
		<include src="s2r://panorama/styles/dashboard_page_profile.vcss_c" />
		<include src="file://{resources}/styles/custom_game/changelog.css" />
	</styles>
	<scripts>
		<include src="file://{resources}/scripts/custom_game/stat_uploader_functions.js" /> 
	    <include src="file://{resources}/scripts/custom_game/changelog.js" /> 
	</scripts>

	<snippets>
		<snippet name="userPic">
			<Panel class="userPicRoot">
				<DOTAAvatarImage class="userPic" id="avatar"/>
				<Panel class="userPicInfo">
					<Panel class="userPicNameFlag">
						<Label id="userPicName" class="userPicName" text="Nickname" />
						<Image id="userPicFlag" />
					</Panel>
					<Label id="userPicDescription" class="userPicDescription" text="Info" />
				</Panel>
				<Panel class="userPicMessages" id="userPicMessages"/>
			</Panel>
		</snippet>
		<snippet name="devMessage">
			<Button class="devMessage">
				<Label class="devMessageLabel" id="devMessageLabel" text="1" />
			</Button>
		</snippet>
	</snippets>

	<Panel class="changelogRoot" hittest="false">
		<Button id="changelogNotification" onactivate='toggleChangelog(toggleCredits)'>
			<Label id="changelogNotificationLabel" text="1" />
		</Button>
		<Panel id="changelogDisplay" class="changelogDisplayHidden" hittest="false">
			<Button id="closeChangelogButton" class="CloseButton" onactivate='toggleChangelog()'>
			</Button>
			<Panel id="Title">
				<Label id="TitleName" text="#addonname" />
				<Label id="SubTitleName" text="#addonname_description" />
				<Panel id="OptionSelect" hittest="false">
					<RadioButton id="showDescriptionButton" class="ProfileContentRightTabOption" text="#lodDescriptionButtonText" onactivate="toggleDescription()"/>
					<Label class="ProfileContentRightTabOptionSeparator" tabindex="auto" text="/" />
					<RadioButton id="showUpdatesButton" class="ProfileContentRightTabOption" text="#lodUpdatesButtonText" onactivate="toggleUpdates()"/>
					<Label class="ProfileContentRightTabOptionSeparator" tabindex="auto" text="/" />
					<RadioButton id="showCreditsButton" class="ProfileContentRightTabOption" text="#lodCreditsButtonText" onactivate="toggleCredits()"/>
				</Panel>
				<Panel class="horizontalSeparator"/>
				<Panel id="currentDisplay" hittest="false" onmouseout="UIHideCustomLayoutTooltip( SendTooltip )">
					<Panel class="displayPanel" id="descriptionDisplay" hittest="false">
						<Panel class="descriptionTextPanel" hittest="false">
							<Label class="displayText" html="true" text="#lodDescriptionText" />
						</Panel>
						<Panel class="submitRoot">
							<Panel class="submitPanel" id="submitInputRoot">
								<TextEntry id="submitInput" multiline="true" textmode="normal" class="submitText" placeholder="#lodMessagePlaceholder" >
								</TextEntry>
							</Panel>
<!-- 							<Panel class="submitPanelTxt">
								<Label class="submitPnlText" text="#lodLeaveComment" />
							</Panel> -->
							<TextButton id="submitButton" class="PlayButton" text="#lodMessageSubmit" onactivate="sendMessage()">
							</TextButton>
						</Panel>
					</Panel>
					<Panel class="displayPanel" id="updateDisplay" hittest="false">
						<Panel class="displayHeader" hittest="false">
							<Panel class="updateClipper" id="updateClipper" hittest="false">
								<Panel class="displayHeader updateEntry" hittest="false">
									<Label class="updateHeaderText" text="2.1 Update" /> 
									<Label class="displayText" text="*Fixed caching of new abilities selected by ingame hero builder\n*Added 17 more Aura's to Elder Titan's Perk. That should be all auras. Let us know if we missed one. Thanks to Squaboonagator for the find\n*Cyclone Trap Reenabled\n*Added 6 abilities from EPIC BOSS FIGHT, including 1 single player ability\n*Fixed the game trying to give players their perks every-time they spawn, even when they already have it\n*Beast-master and CM Perk bonus will not be removed on death any-more\n*Invoker's Perk has a maximum of 30 stacks now\n*Having more than 1 Bash ability is now considered a troll combo\n*Fixed another Shadow Demon Perk abuse\n*Added OP version of charged bolt, intended for single player games.\n*Towers will not have the bot controller ability unless the game has extra tower settings\n*Disable Cyclone Trap for now because its buggy\n*Added a constant mutator to reflect what the current gamemode is. Can only be changed in Custom Settings.\n*LOD and OP bans are now combined into OP bans\n*Single Player bans have been added. These are abilities that REALLY should not be in multiplayer games, and are not balanced and never will be balanced.\n*Returned Imba Towers to their previous powers but added them to single player banlist.\n*Removed SILENCE! from the target of global break. This is not best solution, but had to reduce that sound\n*Abaddon's perk is hidden if he has shield charges. Two buffs for a perk is just clutter\n*Removed the broken player ban option vote\n*If Balance mode is disabled in vote maps, OP abilities will be banned\n*Degen Aura rate lowered by 1%\n*Pocket Factory Goblins acquistion range increased\n*Scout Owl higher duration and automatically follows when cast\n*Stronger Creeps give 8% extra gold instead of 7% per level\n*Mastery of Deception no longer procs from hero attacks\n*Increased price of Betrayal, Tombstone and Global Break\n*Rearm (Original) is now banned on balance mode\n*The Saint's Rage no longer damages buildings\n*Betaryal and Test of Faith is now a troll combo\n*Rifle has more movement speed reduction and higher cooldown\n*Added unique modifier tag to black arrow and added black arrow to the attack modifier category in skill menu\n*Fixed the constant switching back to the Builds page\n*Improved Portal's Castrange\n*Enabled Meepo's Perk\n*Disabled True Random abilities because they are likely causing crashes, enable OP abilities to use them.\n*Fix Shadow Demon Perk Abuse\n*Fix Phoenix Perk Abuse\n*Rename Common Selection to Main Gamemode\n*Vicious Tower and Forest tower are disabled with bots in game. Vicisous kills them too unpredicatably and forest tower screws up their navigation\n*Fixed DragonKnight and Pudge Perk\n*Reworked Wraith King Perk\n*Holy Wrath will not hit buildings\n*Forest IMBA Ability is now a basic ability with 4 levels instead of an ult with 3 levels\n*Increased price of wave form and time walk in balance mode\n*Increased the price of a few of the new custom abilities in balance mode\n*IMBA Tower: Split, Chrono, Laser, Nature, Hex, Permabash, Multihit, Essence and Grevious wounds no longer work against Heros, if the owner is also a hero. Knockback tower will not apply damage but still knocks back.\n*Multihit tower now has 1 second cooldown to prevent attack cancelling abuse.\n*Most Imba abilities will not work on buildings anymore.\n" />
								</Panel>
								<Panel class="horizontalSeparator"/>
							</Panel>
						</Panel>
					</Panel>
					<Panel class="displayPanel" id="creditsDisplay" hittest="false">
						<Panel id="creditsPanel" class="creditsPanel" hittest="false">
						</Panel>
					</Panel>
				</Panel>
			</Panel>		
		</Panel>
	</Panel>
</root>
